You're not getting away.
It's tiny. And hard to target.
Alright, I can do it!
Let's go!
What a horrible voice. My ears. Even so, I can do it. I can beheaded.
What is that? Something's behind me. There's something behind me. Joy, anger, sorrow, pleasure. This doesn't smell like any of them.
Then what's behind me? What do I do? Focus on beheading this one. If I behead this one, then...
It's too hard. I can't slash any further. And the power from Nezuko's blood has run out.
Tanjiro, get down! I can't do it. I made the wrong call.
And because of my position, Genya can't fire his gun without hitting me.
Crap! Here comes the attack!
Natsuko!
Nezuko!
Nezuko, are you alright?
She'll be fine. Her arms and legs have fully regenerated.
You brutal fiends who torment the weak.
You're atrocious, offensive, and despicable.
Damn you all, you awful villains.
Another demon! There's six!
Five's already too many, and we have to fight another one?
Wait, that's not a sixth demon.
The four emotions. There's no trace of them anymore.
What the hell's going on? How many tricks do they have up their sleeve?
I'm positive that one was the anger demon just a second ago!
Something happened. The moment Tanjiro's sword was about to decapitate that tiny demon.
The anger demon raised both of his hands.
And in the blink of an eye, he was able to absorb the joy demon and the pleasure demon.
He pulverized their flesh and then continued absorbing both of them.
Then after drawing them in, the anger demon started sprinting towards Aizitsu.
I saw Aizitsu start to open his mouth as if to protest.
But he was absorbed before he could speak.
The anger demon's body transformed. And turned into that!
You've gotta be kidding me!
He absorbed the three other demons? He fused with them?
Fused with them?
This wasn't a split, but he still got even younger!
He's a kid. A fusion of the demons without the old geezer was most likely the main body!
Oh no! The main body's being surrounded!
Hold it!
It's so overpowering! I can't breathe!
Breathe!
My heart hurts!
What's wrong?
Answer me!
Do you have a problem with what I'm doing or can I continue my duty here?
You have a problem with what I'm doing or can I continue my duty here?
Well?
Do you?
Awful villains?
So heavy.
That voice.
That force!
It's sapping all the strength I have in my limbs!
I can barely stay on my feet!
Tell me...
What makes...
What makes us awful villains?
And not you?
Because you made the choice to torment the weak, right?
Right? Or did you not just try to decapitate a small, weak being who's only big enough to fit in the palm of your hand?
Your actions are utterly atrocious. Only a pure fiend would do something like that.
Did you just say... small and weak?
Small... small and weak?
Don't give me that!
That scent you're giving off right now...
The scent of blood...
A scent like that means you've devoured hundreds of humans!
What did those people do to deserve that fate?
Tell me what they did!
What could they have done that would have cost them their lives?
Don't you dare play the victim card after devouring scores of innocent people!
If there's one thing I'm certain of...
It's that you're evil!
You're the villain!
And I'll be the one that decaminates you!
I'm afraid of someone who has found ghosts!
That demon...
It's a very whispered mystery!
I will ambigu 수도 in life!
I'm too angry either.
You're...
The Однако sous像 donates you!
That demon. It's so overpowering. I still can't move a muscle.
Is that really all you have to say?
I will behead you. No matter what.
Did I kill a family member of yours? Is that why you're so set on beheading me?
No, but...
All right. Then this has nothing to do with you.
You haven't killed anyone dear to me. But that doesn't matter. Because you've slaughtered innocent people who were dear to someone else!
It sounds like you have nothing to do with those people either.
Humans don't need a reason to help out one another!
And if you can't wrap your head around something like that, you're the fiend!
You're the fiend!
I'm the fiend!
Okay, what's the fiend?
Oh, that fake stoic look on your face, how very sublime it is.
My creative juices are simply gushing looking upon it.
Don't get me wrong, I'd love to stick around a little longer and watch as you meet your pathetic end.
But I think it's best I look inside this shack that you are so keen on entering.
I'm trembling with excitement to find out what's inside that you failed to protect.
With the air left inside of my lungs, I should be able to manage one more attack.
Mist breathing. First form. Low clouds distant haze.
Not even that was able to break through it.
It's no wonder given how badly chipped this sword is.
It's futile. It's over.
I can only hope that help is on the way.
Sorry, Master. But I'm going to die. So as soon as you can, please send at least two Hashira.
What makes you think you'll die?
After all, nobody knows what the future holds, right?
Hold on. This isn't right. Tanjiro never said anything like that to me.
If not him, then who?
Stay back! I can't let you get inside!
Yoo-hoo! Why do you bother? You're only wasting my time.
Or could it be that you're foolish enough to think you're capable of fending me off?
Well, I find that to be just carmical.
Why is it you're so desperately defending such a pitiful looking shack?
You wouldn't be hiding your precious village chief in this shed now, would you?
Hmm?
Extraordinary steel. What an extraordinary sword!
That human is young. The body of someone not yet even forty. There's no way he could be chief.
Such brilliant craftsmanship. This blade is stunning.
Hey, human! What are you doing over there?
Who created this masterpiece? By what kind of person was this sword forged?
And why did he carve this single character rather than his own name?
No. I understand. I understand why.
Damn him!
I've never seen such razor sharp focus. He's so immersed in what he's doing that he's still unaware of me.
I don't like this one bit.
Even I've never concentrated this hard on one of my pieces.
As an artist, I can't help but feel inferior to him.
Stop it!
Mr. Hageneska!
This single character tells me this sword was forged with nothing but pure determination!
I understand it now. This sword was forged for this sole purpose and nothing else!
Mr. Hageneska!
I can't stand this guy. It would be Child's Blade to horrifically slaughter him.
But what I want right now is to make this man abandon that sword!
I want to shatter his concentration!
My vision is starting to get distorted. I'm dying. I'm all out of air.
Sorry, but it's not for you to decide when it's all over.
I don't understand. You never told me that.
It's all gonna be okay. Just don't give up. I promise someone's gonna save you.
Really? Leave it to someone else? That's the worst thing I could do.
There's a limit to what we can do. At least when we're alone. We all need help. There's no shame in asking for it.
But there's no one who can save me. Because everyone's weaker than I am.
I'm the one who should've been stronger.
I misjudged my strength. And subconsciously overestimated my own skills. All because I'm a Hashira.
You're not wrong about that, Muichiro. You're gonna be fine.
I'm going to die because that's not the only mistake I made.
Mr. Tokito!
We won't let you die! Hang in there, Mr. Tokito! No matter what, I'm gonna get you out of there and steam you!
C-Cram! What is this? It's so rubbery and disgusting!
If even I can't slash through it, how on earth can you?
Not to mention you have bigger priorities than me right now. You have to protect the Chief.
Oh, I suppose that would be beyond you. You should grab as many swords as you can and run.
What are you doing? Behind you! Behind you! Behind you!
I'm bleeding!
What are you doing? What are you doing? Make a run for it! Before it's too late!
His solar plexus. He got stabbed in his vital point. He's going to die.
Why don't you get it? You're not strong enough! Put pressure on that wound and get out of here already!
Stop trying to save me! You need to save yourself! There's nothing you can do for me!
What're you doing?!
Life always rewards good deeds. When you help others, you're often helping yourself.
Humans are incredible.
They can summon an unbelievable strength, but only when it's for the sake of someone
other than themselves.
Muichiro.
Yes, I know.
Mist-breathing second form.
Eight-layered mist!
I remember now, Tanjiro.
The reason I saw you, but heard my father's words.
It's because you share the same red eyes.
I call the element to be my life.
I've been looking for forever.
Where do I go from?
I've never been to the end of the night.
Thank you.
The knives he was wielding when he chased after Mr. Tanjiro were forged by Mr. Hageneska.
But since they're unbelievably sharp, he says he's too scared to use them for cooking.
Is that totally pointless or what?
Mr. Hageneska!
Scary, scary, scary!
Mr. Hageneska, you're scaring me!
Next episode 8, the Moo in Mooichiro!